A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers, Inc. (RBI) (and successors) records FA480
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Investments, A-Z, Accession 2, 1949-1976; 2; 22.77 Cubic Feet 55 letter document boxes and 4 legal document boxes; Standard storage boxes, Boxes 115-135.
  - Itek - Stock Option, 1957-1969 (Box 314, Folder 5, Box 315, Folder 1-3, Box 316, Folder 1)
  - Kin and Company - Dissolution of, 1971 (Box 316, Folder 2)
  - Kin and Company - Agreement of Partnership, 1967 (Box 316, Folder 3)
  - Kin and Company - Investment Information, 1967-1971 (Box 316, Folder 4-6, Box 317, Folder 1-2)
  - Kin and Company - Partnership Meetings, 1967-1970 (Box 317, Folder 3)
  - Kin and Company - Position Paper, 1967 (Box 317, Folder 4)
  - Kin and Company - Quarterly Reports to Partners, 1967-1970 (Box 317, Folder 5)
  - Kin and Company - Stock Transaction Sheets, 1967-1971 (Box 317, Folder 6)
  - Kin and Company - SEC, 1963-1968 (Box 317, Folder 7)
  - Kin and Company - Transfer of Securities to Venrock (Box 317, Folder 8)
  - Kin and Company - Summary (Box 318, Folder 1)
  - Larson Industries, 1966-1970 (Box 318, Folder 2)
  - Longstreet Corp., 1964-1965 (Box 318, Folder 3)
  - Lykes-Youngstown - Board of Directors Meetings, 1967-1970 (Box 318, Folder 4)
  - Middle East Industrial Project (MIDEC), 1958-1972 (Box 318, Folder 5)
  - Marks Polarized Corp., 1966 (Box 318, Folder 6)
  - New England Nuclear - Iso-Med Agreement, 1971 (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - New England Nuclear - Board of Directors Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 319, Folder 2)
  - New England Nuclear - Board of Directors Meetings, 1961-1972 (Box 319, Folder 3-6)
  - New England Nuclear - Financial Audits, 1967-1972 (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - New England Nuclear - Financing - Public Offering, 1967 (Box 320, Folder 2)
  - New England Nuclear - Financing, 1961-1969 (Box 320, Folder 3)
  - New England Nuclear - General, 1961-1972 (Box 320, Folder 4)
  - New England Nuclear - Mergers, 1965-1972 (Box 320, Folder 5)
  - New England Nuclear - Picker-Nuclear Joint Venture, 1965-1966 (Box 320, Folder 6)
  - New England Nuclear - Stock Holder and Stock Option, 1961-1971 (Box 321, Folder 1)
  - New England Nuclear - Summary, 1973 (Box 321, Folder 2)
  - New York Airways, 1964-1968 (Box 321, Folder 3)
  - New York Airways - Summary, 1962 (Box 321, Folder 4)
  - Optomechanisms, Inc. - Board of Directors Meetings and Correspondence, 1960-1970 (Box 321, Folder 5)
  - Optomechanisms, Inc. - All Financial Reports, 1960-1972 (Box 322, Folder 1)
  - Optomechanisms, Inc. - Financing, 1964-1971 (Box 322, Folder 2)
  - Optomechanisms, Inc. - Original Financing, 1960-1962 (Box 322, Folder 3)
  - Optomechanisms, Inc. - General, 1966-1972 (Box 322, Folder 4)
  - Optomechanisms, Inc. - Shareholders, 1960-1972 (Box 322, Folder 5)
  - Optomechanisms, Inc. - Stock Options, 1961-1967 (Box 323, Folder 1)
  - Optomechanisms, Inc. - Summary (Box 323, Folder 2)
  - PEK Labs.,Inc., 1967-1969 (Box 323, Folder 3)
  - William D. Pardrige, 1951-1965 (Box 323, Folder 4)
  - Quotron Systems, Inc. - Board of Directors Meetings, 1966-1970 (Box 323, Folder 5)
    Name changed from Scantlin Electronics
  - Quotron Systems, Inc. - Executive Committee Meetings, 1966-1970 (Box 323, Folder 6)
  - Quotron Systems, Inc. - Correspondence - General, 1958-1969 (Box 324, Folder 1)
  - Quotron Systems, Inc. - Mergers - General, 1969-1971 (Box 324, Folder 2)
  - Quotron Systems, Inc. - Mergers - Istar, 1959-1961 (Box 323, Folder 7)
  - Rockwell Breda Discussions, 1958-1961 (Box 324, Folder 3)
  - Sanders Associates, Inc. - Takeover of Mithras, 1965-1970 (Box 324, Folder 4, Box 325, Folder 1)
  - Scientific Atlantic Inc. - Financing, 1960-1967 (Box 325, Folder 2)
  - Societe Des Ciments D'Outremer, 1953-1968 (Box 325, Folder 3)
  - Societe Pour Le Development et Expansion D'Enterprises (SDE), 1951-1970 (Box 325, Folder 4)
  - Societe du Pipe-Line Sud-European (South European Pipeline Co.), 1960 (Box 326, Folder 1)
  - Sunrise Aircraft Corp. of America, 1965-1966 (Box 326, Folder 2)
  - System Development Corp., 1968-1969 (Box 326, Folder 3)
  - James Talcott, 1964-1966 (Box 326, Folder 4)
  - Edward Teller, 1960-1971 (Box 326, Folder 5)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Agendas, 1969-1972 (Box 326, Folder 6, Box 327, Folder 1-2)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Board of Directors Meetings, 1965-1967 (Box 327, Folder 3)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Board of Directors Minutes, 1968-1972 (Box 327, Folder 4, Box 328, Folder 1)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - General, 1960-1970 (Box 328, Folder 2)
  - Thiokol Chemical Corp. - Agreements, 1959-1966 (Box 328, Folder 3)
  - Thiokol Chemical Corp. - Articles of Incorporation, By-laws, 1958-1966 (Box 328, Folder 4)
  - Thiokol Chemical Corp. - Board of Directors Meetings, 1967 (Box 328, Folder 5)
  - Thiokol Chemical Corp. - Executive Committee Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 328, Folder 6)
  - Thiokol Chemical Corp. - General, 1962-1969 (Box 328, Folder 7)
  - Thiokol Chemical Corp. - Mergers, 1966-1967 (Box 328, Folder 8)
  - Thiokol Chemical Corp. - Prospectus, 1958-1966 (Box 328, Folder 9)
  - Thiokol Chemical Corp. - Stock Option, 1958-1965 (Box 329, Folder 1)
  - Thiokol Chemical Corp. - Summary, 1966 (Box 329, Folder 2)
  - Thirty Rockefeller Plaza Assoc. and Co., 1963-1966 (Box 329, Folder 3)
  - Transoceanic AOFC Ltd., 1958-1961 (Box 329, Folder 4, Box 330, Folder 1)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - SEC, 1961-1968 (Box 330, Folder 2)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Bokum Corp. Acquisition Offering, 1967-1968 (Box 330, Folder 3-4)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Richard D. Bokum II, Agreement, 1966-1967 (Box 330, Folder 5)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Summary, 1962-1964 (Box 331, Folder 1)
  - Ventron - Board of Directors Meetings, 1967-1970 (Box 331, Folder 2-3)
  - Vermont International Airways, 1971 (Box 331, Folder 4)
  - Vitro Corporation of America, 1959-1965 (Box 331, Folder 5)
  - Vitro Corporation of America - Summary Folder, 1959-1965 (Box 331, Folder 6)
  - Whitney Operations, Inc. - Financing, 1969-1970 (Box 331, Folder 7)
  - Whitney Operations, Inc. - General, 1969-1970 (Box 331, Folder 8)
  - Whitney Operations, Inc. - Summary, 1969-1970 (Box 332, Folder 1)
  - E. Burke Wilford, 1951-1969 (Box 332, Folder 2)
- Investments, A-Z, Accession 3, 1948-1979; 3; 22.1 Cubic Feet 52 letter document boxes and 5 legal document boxes.; Standard storage boxes, Boxes 142-164.
  - Aerovox Corp. - Agreement 1966, 5.5 Percent Convertible Sub. Debentures (Box 333, Folder 1)
  - Aerovox Corp. - Agreement 1971, 5.5 Percent Convertible Sub. Debentures, 1971 December (Box 333, Folder 2)
  - Aerovox Corp. - Correspondence re 5.5 Percent Sub. Debentures, 1966-1971 (Box 333, Folder 3)
  - Aerovox Corp. - Belleville Ind. Inc. Purchase Agreement, 1972 December (Box 333, Folder 4)
  - Aerovox Corp. - Agreement - CSI (Box 333, Folder 5)
  - Aerovox Corp. - Agreement San Fernando Mfg. Co. License Agreement (Box 333, Folder 6)
  - Aerovox Corp. - Articles of Incorporation, By-Laws (Box 333, Folder 7)
  - Aerovox Corp. - Board of Directors Correspondence, 1972 (Box 334, Folder 1)
  - Aerovox Corp. - Board of Directors Meetings, 1968-1973 (Box 334, Folder 2-3)
  - Aerovox Corp. - Essex Wire Corp. (Box 334, Folder 4)
  - Aerovox Corp. - Financial (Box 334, Folder 5)
  - Aerovox Corp. - General - Sale of Assets, 1972 (Box 334, Folder 6)
  - Aerovox Corp. - General - Annuals, Prospectus, 1972 (Box 335, Folder 1)
  - Aerovox Corp. - Investment Agreements, 1974 (Box 335, Folder 2)
  - Aerovox Corp. - Profit Sharing, 1973 (Box 335, Folder 3)
  - Aerovox Corp. - Shareholders, 1973 (Box 335, Folder 4)
  - Aerovox Corp. - Stock Option, 1969-1973 (Box 335, Folder 5)
  - American European Association - 56-40 Partnership, 1970-1971 (Box 335, Folder 6)
  - American European Association - Financing - Agreement Letter (Box 335, Folder 7)
  - American European Association - General, 1969-1974 (Box 336, Folder 1-2)
  - American European Association - Communication with Principals, 1966-1969 (Box 336, Folder 3)
  - American European Association - Investment Considerations (Box 336, Folder 4)
  - American Regitel Corp., 1972-1974 (Box 337, Folder 1)
  - Atlantic Aviation Corp. - Sale of Atlantic shares to Executive Jet, 1970 (Box 337, Folder 2)
  - Atlantic Aviation Corp. - Annuals and Stockholders, 1970 (Box 337, Folder 3)
  - Atlantic Aviation Corp. - Financing, 1970 (Box 337, Folder 4)
  - Atlantic Aviation Corp. - General, 1970 (Box 337, Folder 5)
  - Billings Farms Inc. - Financial, 1965-1973 (Box 338, Folder 1)
  - Billings Farms Inc. - General, 1954-1973 (Box 338, Folder 2)
  - Blackside, 1970s (Box 338, Folder 3)
  - Blue Meridian - David Rockefeller Investment, 1965-1971 (Box 332, Folder 3-4)
  - Blue Meridian - General, 1965-1971 (Box 332, Folder 5)
  - Blue Meridian - Clippings, 1965-1971 (Box 332, Folder 6)
  - Blue Meridian - Correspondence, 1965-1972 (Box 332, Folder 7)
  - Blue Meridian - Prospects, 1965-1969 (Box 332, Folder 8)
  - Cabot, Cabot and Forbes, 1971-1972 (Box 338, Folder 4)
  - Cegeac, 1961-1973 (Box 339, Folder 1)
  - Chrysler Corporation - J.R. Dilworth Correspondence, 1961-1973 (Box 339, Folder 2)
  - Clarcan Petroleum - Agreement, Articles of Incorporation, 1971-1973 (Box 339, Folder 3)
  - Clarcan Petroleum - Annual Reports, 1971-1973 (Box 339, Folder 4)
  - Clarcan Petroleum - Board of Directors Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 339, Folder 5)
  - Clarcan Petroleum - Board of Directors, 1970-1974 (Box 339, Folder 6, Box 340, Folder 1)
  - Clarcan Petroleum - Cofan (Box 340, Folder 2)
  - Clarcan Petroleum - Financial, 1972-1973 (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - Clarcan Petroleum - General, 1970-1974 (Box 340, Folder 4)
  - Clarcan Petroleum - Peter Crisp notes re: Takeover of Clark Canadian Exploration Co., 1970-1971 (Box 340, Folder 5)
  - Clarcan Petroleum Corp. - Prospectus, 1972-1973 (Box 340, Folder 6)
  - Clarcan Petroleum - Clark Canadian - Takeover Corres. American Resources, 1971-1972; C (Box 341, Folder 1)
  - Clarcan Petroleum Corp. - Merger Prospects (Box 341, Folder 2)
  - Clarcan Petroleum Corp. - Mergers - Ladd Petroleum, Utah International (Box 341, Folder 3)
  - Clarcan Petroleum Corp. - Summary, 1974 (Box 341, Folder 4)
  - Clarcan Petroleum Corp. - Exchange Agreement Clark Canadian, 1970-1972 (Box 342, Folder 1-2)
  - Publicate - Proposed sale of assets to Comnet, 1970-1973 (Box 343, Folder 1)
  - Comnet - Annual Reports - Shareholders, 1970-1973 (Box 343, Folder 2)
  - Comnet - Financial Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 343, Folder 3)
  - Comnet - Financing, 1969-1970 (Box 343, Folder 4)
  - Comnet - General, 1969-1973 (Box 343, Folder 5)
  - Comnet - Prospectus, 1971 (Box 343, Folder 6)
  - Comnet - Summary, 1974 (Box 343, Folder 7)
  - Comtel Corp. - Summary, 1975 (Box 343, Folder 8)
  - Comtel Corp. - Bankruptcy Chapter XI, 1972 (Box 343, Folder 9)
  - Comtel Corp. - Board of Directors Meetings, 1970 (Box 344, Folder 1)
  - Comtel Corp. - Financial Correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box 344, Folder 2)
  - Comtel Corp. - Financing, 1968-1971 (Box 344, Folder 3)
  - Comtel Corp. - General, 1968-1976 (Box 344, Folder 4)
  - Comtel Corp. - Stockholder - Stock Options, 1969-1972 (Box 344, Folder 5)
  - Data Science Ventures - Meeting Notes, 1972-1974 (Box 344, Folder 6)
  - Data Science Ventures - Summary, 1973 (Box 345, Folder 1)
  - Data Science Ventures - Stockholder - Liquidation of Corporation, 1974-1975 (Box 345, Folder 2-3)
  - Data Science Ventures - Annuals and Shareholders, 1969-1974 (Box 345, Folder 4)
  - Data Science Ventures - Agendas, 1972-1974 (Box 345, Folder 5-6)
  - Data Science Ventures - Board of Directors - Agendas, 1969-1971 (Box 342, Folder 3-4)
  - Data Science Ventures - Board of Directors Meetings - Minutes, 1968-1974 (Box 346, Folder 1-2)
  - Data Science Ventures - Executive Committee Meetings, 1970-1974 (Box 342, Folder 5)
  - Data Science Ventures - Financial Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 346, Folder 3)
  - Data Science Ventures - Original Financing, 1968-1969 (Box 346, Folder 4)
  - Data Science Ventures - General, 1968-1973 (Box 346, Folder 5)
  - Data Science Ventures - Investment Opportunities, 1968-1974 (Box 347, Folder 1-2)
  - Diamond Shamrock Corp. - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 347, Folder 3)
  - Diamond Shamrock Corp. - Board of Directors Meetings and Agendas, 1971-1973 (Box 347, Folder 4)
  - Diamond Shamrock Corp. - Board of Directors Meetings - Minutes, 1970-1972 (Box 347, Folder 5)
  - Diamond Shamrock Corp. - Prospectus - Options - Debentures, 1969-1974 (Box 348, Folder 1)
  - Eastern Airlines - Board of Directors and Finance Committee Meetings - Minutes, 1972 (Box 348, Folder 2-3)
  - Eastern Airlines - Board of Directors and Finance Committee Meetings - Minutes, 1973 (Box 348, Folder 4-5, Box 349, Folder 1-4, Box 350, Folder 1-5)
  - Eastern Airlines - Board of Directors and Finance Committee Meetings - Minutes, 1974 (Box 351, Folder 1-4, Box 352, Folder 1-5, Box 353)
  - Eastern Airlines - Board of Directors and Finance Committee Meetings - Minutes, 1975 (Box 354, Folder 1-4, Box 355, Box 356, Folder 1-5)
  - Fansteel Inc. - By-Laws (Box 357, Folder 1)
  - Fansteel Inc. - Board of Directors, 1968-1972 (Box 357, Folder 2)
  - Fansteel Inc. - General, 1966-1971 (Box 357, Folder 3)
  - Fansteel Inc. - Financing Convertible Sub. Note, 1967-1974 (Box 357, Folder 4)
  - Fansteel Inc. - Stock Option Plan, 1968-1971 (Box 357, Folder 5)
  - Flight Safety Foundation - By-Laws, Corporate Documents (Box 357, Folder 6)
  - Flight Safety Foundation - Awards, 1959-1964 (Box 357, Folder 7)
  - Flight Safety Foundation - Fund Raising, 1966-1973 (Box 358, Folder 1)
  - Flight Safety Foundation - General, 1968-1974 (Box 358, Folder 2)
  - Flight Safety Foundation - Meetings, 1971-1976 (Box 358, Folder 3)
  - Flight Safety Foundation - Miscellaneous Safety Notes, 1960s (Box 358, Folder 4)
  - Flight Safety Foundation - Annual Reports, 1948-1976 (Box 358, Folder 5-6)
  - GAB Business Service - Board of Directors Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 359, Folder 1)
  - GAB Business Service - Financial Audit Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 359, Folder 2)
  - GAB Service Inc. - Marshall and Stevens Report, 1972 (Box 359, Folder 3)
  - GAB Business Service - Agendas, 1973-1975 (Box 359, Folder 4-5)
  - GAB Service Inc. - General, 1972 (Box 360, Folder 1)
  - GAB Service Inc. - Shareholders, 1975 (Box 360, Folder 2)
  - GCA Corp. - Financial - Audits, 1962-1971 (Box 360, Folder 3)
  - GCA Corp. - Financing, 1958-1963 (Box 361, Folder 1)
  - GCA Corp. - General Correspondence, 1963-1971 (Box 360, Folder 4)
  - GCA Corp. - Mergers - General, 1971-1973 (Box 360, Folder 5)
  - GCA Corp. - Mergers - Prospects, 1969-1970 (Box 361, Folder 2)
  - GCA Corp. - Mergers - Gosslin Birmingham (Box 361, Folder 3)
  - GCA Corp. - Mergers - Industrial Modular Systems Corp., 1972 (Box 361, Folder 4)
  - GCA Corp. - Mergers - David W. Mann, Inc. (Box 361, Folder 5)
  - GCA Corp. - Mergers - Markite Corporation, 1969-1972 (Box 362, Folder 1)
  - GCA Corp. - Mergers - Norton Vacuum Equipment Division, 1963-1970 (Box 362, Folder 2)
  - GCA Corp. - Mergers - Precision Scientific Co. (Box 362, Folder 3)
  - GCA Corp. - Mergers - Vacuum Industries Inc. (Box 362, Folder 4)
  - GCA Corp. - Prospectus, 1960-1967 (Box 362, Folder 5)
  - GCA Corp. - Public Offering, 1958-1960 (Box 362, Folder 6)
  - GCA Corp. - Small Business Administration, 1962 (Box 363, Folder 1)
  - GCA Corp. - SEC Forms 3 and 4 Initial Statement of Ownership, 1962-1970 (Box 363, Folder 2)
  - GCA Corp. - Stock Exchange Listing, 1963 (Box 363, Folder 3)
  - GCA Corp. - Summary, 1962-1967 (Box 363, Folder 4)
  - Inflight Devices Corp. - Investment Agreement, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 5)
  - Inflight Devices Corp. - Agreement - Edo Corp., 1973 (Box 363, Folder 6)
  - Inflight Devices Corp. - Agreement - Cyrus W. Brown, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 7)
  - Inflight Devices Corp. - Astronautics Corp. of America, 1973 (Box 363, Folder 8)
  - Inflight Devices Corp. - Board of Directors Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 363, Folder 9)
  - Inflight Devices Corp. - Financial (All), 1972-1974 (Box 363, Folder 10)
  - Inflight Devices Corp. - Financing - Agreement - Lease (Box 363, Folder 11)
  - Inflight Devices Corp. - Financing - Documents, 1972 April (Box 364, Folder 1)
  - Inflight Devices Corp. - Financing - Private Placement Memo, 1973 (Box 364, Folder 2)
  - Inflight Devices Corp. - Financing - May 1973 Promissory Note, 1973 May (Box 364, Folder 3)
  - Inflight Devices Corp. - Financing - December 1972 Five Year 6 Percent Convertible Subordinated, 1972 December (Box 364, Folder 4)
  - Inflight Devices Corp. - General, 1973-1974 (Box 364, Folder 5)
  - Inflight Devices Corp. - Shareholders, 1972-1973 (Box 364, Folder 6)
  - Institute for Advanced Study - General, 1975 (Box 364, Folder 7)
  - Institute for Advanced Study - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 364, Folder 8)
  - Institute for Advanced Study - Financial Statements, 1967-1970 (Box 365, Folder 1)
  - Institute for Advanced Study - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1966-1968; 1972 (Box 365, Folder 2)
  - Instron Corp., 1966-1974 (Box 365, Folder 3)
  - Irvine Research, 1972 (Box 365, Folder 4)
  - Iomec Corp. - Summary, 1969 (Box 365, Folder 5)
  - Iomec Corp. - Investments - Agreement, 1971-1977 (Box 365, Folder 6)
  - Iomec Corp. - Merger Agreements - Warrant to Purchase Common Stock, 1972 (Box 366, Folder 1)
  - Iomec Corp. - Wells Fargo Financing Agreement, 1974 (Box 366, Folder 2)
  - Iomec Corp. - Financial - Audits, 1969-1975 (Box 366, Folder 3)
  - Iomec Corp. - Financial - Correspondence, 1968-1975 (Box 366, Folder 4)
  - Iomec Corp. - Annual Reports, 1969-1973 (Box 366, Folder 5)
  - Iomec Corp. - Board of Directors - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 366, Folder 6)
  - Iomec Corp. - Board of Directors - Meetings - Minutes, 1969-1975 (Box 366, Folder 7)
  - Iomec Inc. - Financing - Investment Letters, 1975 December (Box 366, Folder 8)
  - Iomec Corp. - Board of Directors - Agendas, 1969-1975 (Box 367, Folder 1-2)
  - Iomec Inc. - Financing - Wells Fargo, 1975 April-May (Box 367, Folder 3)
  - Iomec Inc. - Financing, 1974 April-June (Box 367, Folder 4)
  - Iomec Inc. - Financing - Conversion of 6 Percent Debentures, 1970 July (Box 367, Folder 5)
  - Iomec Inc. - Financing - Conversion of 6 Percent Debentures, 1972 July (Box 368, Folder 1)
  - Iomec Inc. - Financing - 6 Percent Convertible Debentures, 1971 January 29 (Box 368, Folder 2)
  - Iomec Inc. - Financing - Start Up, 1968 (Box 368, Folder 3)
  - Iomec Inc. - Financing - Legal Documents, 1968 (Box 368, Folder 4)
  - Iomec Inc. - General - Clippings, News Releases, 1968-1975 (Box 368, Folder 5)
  - Iomec Inc. - Peter O. Crisp - Logs of Contacts, 1974-1975 (Box 369, Folder 1)
  - Iomec Inc. - Mergers - General, 1970-1974 (Box 369, Folder 2)
  - Iomec Inc. - Private Placement Memo - Business Plan, 1970-1974 (Box 369, Folder 3)
  - Iomec Inc. - Shareholders Meetings, 1969-1974 (Box 369, Folder 4)
  - Iomec Inc. - Shareholders, 1968-1975 (Box 369, Folder 5)
  - Iomec Inc. - Stock Option Committee Minutes, 1969-1973 (Box 369, Folder 6)
  - Iomec Inc. - Stock Option Plan, 1968-1971 (Box 369, Folder 7)
  - Iomec Inc., 1968 (Box 370, Folder 1)
  - Itek Corp. - Executive Committee Board of Directors, 1961-1973 (Box 370, Folder 2)
  - Itek Corp. - Board of Directors Meetings, 1972-1974 (Box 370, Folder 3-5)
  - Itek Corp. - Finance and Audit, 1968-1974 (Box 371, Folder 1)
  - Itek Corp. - General, 1968-1974 (Box 371, Folder 2-3)
  - Itek Corp. - Mergers - Encyclopaedia Britannica, 1969 (Box 371, Folder 4)
  - Itek Corp. - Mergers - General, 1965-1968 (Box 371, Folder 5)
  - Itek Corp. - Mergers - General, 1969-1972 (Box 372, Folder 1-2)
  - Itek Corp. - Mergers - Helio Associates, 1971-1972 (Box 372, Folder 3)
  - Itek Corp. - Mergers - Pennsylvania Optical, 1965-1971 (Box 372, Folder 4)
  - Itek Corp. - Mergers - Polychrome, 1971-1973 (Box 373, Folder 1)
  - Itek Corp. - Stock Option Plan, 1970-1972 (Box 373, Folder 2-3)
  - Intercontinental Systems Inc. - Summary, 1969 (Box 373, Folder 4)
    Name changed to Intel Corp.
  - Intercontinental Systems Inc. - Agreements, 1966-1968 (Box 373, Folder 5)
  - Intercontinental Systems Inc. - Financing, 1967-1969 (Box 374, Folder 1)
  - Intercontinental Systems Inc. - Original Financing Papers, 1967 (Box 374, Folder 2)
  - Intel Corp. - Stakeholders Proxy, 1967-1972 (Box 374, Folder 3)
  - Intel Corp. - Intercontinental Merger - 1970 Negotiations (Box 374, Folder 4)
  - Intel Corp. - Annual Reports, 1970-1973 (Box 375, Folder 1)
  - Intel Corp. - Board of Directors Meetings, 1968-1971 (Box 375, Folder 2-4)
  - Intel Corp. - Financial Reports - Financial Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 375, Folder 5)
  - Intel Corp. - Prospectus, 1968-1971 (Box 375, Folder 6)
  - Intel Corp. - General, 1968-1970 (Box 376, Folder 1)
  - Intel Corp. - Stock Option Plan, 1969 (Box 376, Folder 2)
  - Lee Laboratories, 1975 (Box 376, Folder 3)
  - Lee Laboratories - Financial, 1968-1974 (Box 376, Folder 4)
  - Lee Laboratories - General, 1968-1974 (Box 376, Folder 5)
  - Lee Laboratories - Stockholder Meetings, 1969-1975 (Box 376, Folder 6)
  - Charles Watson Newhall, 1966 (Box 377, Folder 1)
  - Omega Fund - Board of Directors Meetings, 1969-1972 (Box 377, Folder 2-3)
  - Pocantico Hills International - General, 1965-1970 (Box 377, Folder 4)
    Includes By-laws
  - Pocantico Hills International - Board of Directors and Stockholders, 1965-1969 (Box 378, Folder 1)
  - Pocantico Oil and Gas - Board of Directors and Stockholders (CES), 1961-1970 (Box 378, Folder 2)
  - Pocantico Oil and Gas - Audits, 1965-1968 (Box 378, Folder 3)
  - Programming Sciences Corp., 1970 (Box 377, Folder 5)
  - Quotron Systems - Agreement Bank Loan (Box 378, Folder 4)
  - Quotron Systems - Agreement Ultronic Systems Corp. (Box 378, Folder 5)
  - Quotron Systems - Agreement Transaction Technology (Box 379, Folder 1)
  - Quotron Systems - Board of Directors - Agendas, 1967-1973 (Box 379, Folder 2)
  - Quotron Systems - Board of Directors - Meetings, 1971-1973 (Box 379, Folder 3)
  - Quotron Systems - Compensation Plan, 1966-1972 (Box 379, Folder 4)
  - Quotron Systems - Articles of Incorporation, By-Laws, 1964 (Box 379, Folder 5)
  - Quotron Systems - Dow Jones and Co. Inc., 1964-1971 (Box 379, Folder 6, Box 380, Folder 1)
  - Quotron Systems - Financial Audits, 1959-1967 (Box 380, Folder 2)
  - Quotron Systems - Financial Dun and Bradstreet, 1967-1973 (Box 380, Folder 3)
  - Quotron Systems - Financing, 1958-1963 (Box 380, Folder 4)
  - Quotron Systems - Financing, 1964-1967 (Box 380, Folder 5)
  - Quotron Systems - Financing, 1969 (Box 381, Folder 1)
  - Quotron Systems - Financing, 1972 (Box 381, Folder 2)
  - Quotron Systems - Stock Option Plan, 1958-1972 (Box 381, Folder 3-4)
  - Quotron Systems - Stockholders, 1965-1972 (Box 381, Folder 5)
  - Quotron Systems - Stockholders Meetings, 1959-1973 (Box 381, Folder 6)
    Includes proxy.
  - Research and Science Investors, 1969-1974 (Box 382, Folder 1)
  - Syndicat Pour L'Etude Geologique and Miniere De La Cuvette Congolaise, 1961-1972 (Box 382, Folder 2)
  - Scidata Inc. - Investment Agreements (Box 386, Folder 1)
  - Scidata Inc. - Board of Directors Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 382, Folder 3)
  - Scidata Inc. - Financial Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 382, Folder 4)
  - Scidata Inc. - Financing, 1972 September (Box 382, Folder 5)
  - Scidata Inc. - Financing, 1973 June 22 (Box 382, Folder 6)
  - Scidata Inc. - Financing, 1974 April 26 (Box 383, Folder 1)
  - Scidata Inc. - General, 1972-1974 (Box 383, Folder 2)
  - Scidata Inc. - Merger - Prospects (Box 383, Folder 3)
  - Scidata Inc. - Merger - Computer Usage Corp., 1974-1975 (Box 383, Folder 4)
  - Scidata Inc. - Stockholders, 1973 (Box 383, Folder 5)
  - Scidata Inc. - Gary A. Stoltz and Associates, 1973-1975 (Box 383, Folder 6)
  - Ventron Corp. - Board of Directors Meetings, 1971-1974 (Box 384, Folder 1)